{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521761481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521761481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-10-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521767240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521767240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-10-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521772968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521772967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-10-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521777712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521777712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521783896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521783896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_2-11-13"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521789147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521789147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-0-11"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521795363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521795363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-0-11"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521801163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521801163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521806123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521806122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_10-5-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521811980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521811980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_10-5-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521816469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521816469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-10-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521820779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521820779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-10-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521826438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521826438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-10-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521832801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521832801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-10-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521837702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521837702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521842285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521842285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-11-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521848717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521848717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-11-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521855390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521855390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 40cb474c-f134-40ca-814b-4cff25eb8610"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-11-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521867092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521867092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521867664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521867664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521868376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521868376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521868549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521868549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521869322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521869322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521870344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521870344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521873176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521873176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TULIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521873859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521873859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" FOLENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521875112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521875112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521876775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521876775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521877498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521877498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" KUCHOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521878341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521878341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521879204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521879204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521879927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521879926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521880590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521880590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521884171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521884171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TULISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521884716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521884715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521884864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521884863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521885269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521885268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521886106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521886106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521887035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521887034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" KUPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521887734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521887733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521887887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521887887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521888654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521888653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521891739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521891738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TULIFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521892224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521892222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521892748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521892747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521893537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521893537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521894192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521894191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521894845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521894845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521894934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521894934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521895541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521895540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" WIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521898690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521898690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521898834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521898833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521899777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521899777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521900857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521900856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521901525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521901524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521901983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521901983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521902628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521902627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521903174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521903173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521903661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521903660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521905045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521905045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521905708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521905707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" KULIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521906306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521906305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521909304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521909304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521909689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521909688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521910683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521910682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521911204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521911203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521912179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521912178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521912834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521912834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521913463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521913462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" YAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521916454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521916454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521917216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521917216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521918042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521918042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" WALIRANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521918549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521918546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" RANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521919495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521919495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521920141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521920141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521920758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521920758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521921709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521921708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521922165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521922164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521922637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521922637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521923619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521923618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MASHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521926699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521926699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521928006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521928005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIPOVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521929749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521929748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521930554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521930554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521931393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521931393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" CHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521931869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521931869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521933098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521933097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" KUZIANGIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521934139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521934139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521934606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521934605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521935232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521935232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" UANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521938686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521938685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521939291","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521939291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521940224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521940224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521940415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521940413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521941163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521941160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521941420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521941419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521942060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521942059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521943459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521943458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521943812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521943812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521944309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521944306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521947888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521947888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521948341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521948341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521948993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521948993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521950290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521950289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521950495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521950494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521951104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521951103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521952343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521952342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521953039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521953038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521953898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521953897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" MITUNGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521954332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521954331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521955481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521955480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521956210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521956209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521959301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521959300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521960553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521960552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521961329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521961328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521961961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521961960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521962747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521962747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521963312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521963312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521964628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521964627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" AKIWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521965149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521965149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521966400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521966400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521967223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521967223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521967437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521967437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521968251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521968251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" KUJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521971066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521971065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521972322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521972322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521972902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521972901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521972990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521972990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521973428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521973427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521973991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521973990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521974395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521974394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521975329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521975329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521976195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521976195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TULIPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521976776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521976775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521977035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521977034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521977805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521977804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521980809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521980809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521981705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521981705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521982830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521982830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521983315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521983315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521984193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521984192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" KIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521984601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521984601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521985351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521985350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521986672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521986672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521987894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521987893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TUREKEBISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521988454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521988453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521989104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521989103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521992580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521992579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521993796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521993795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521994664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521994663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" AMEPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521995280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521995279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521996209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521996208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521996502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521996501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521997167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521997167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521998210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521998210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521999309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521999309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" KUSAFISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521999959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521999957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522000119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522000119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522000537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522000537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522001258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522001257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522004355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522004354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522004915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522004914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522005100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522005099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522005879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522005878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" MAKAMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522006700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522006699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522007678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522007677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522008647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522008646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522009653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522009652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522010416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522010415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" KUUNGANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522010611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522010611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522011221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522011220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522012023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522012022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522015037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522015036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522015879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522015878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522016847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522016846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522017051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522017050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522017705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522017705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522018898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522018897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522019809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522019808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" WATACHIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522020388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522020387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522020649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522020648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522021347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522021346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522024508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522024508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522025395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522025394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISEMA"," userResponse":" TULISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522025639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522025638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522026301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522026301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522026796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522026796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522028172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522028171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522029306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522029305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUBADILISHE"," userResponse":" TUBADILISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522030041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522030040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522030749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522030748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522033131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522033131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522033604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522033604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522034247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522034246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522035323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522035323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522035809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522035808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522036797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522036796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522038197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522038197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATATUA"," userResponse":" TUKATATUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522038694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522038694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522039060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522039059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522041949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522041947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522042026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522042026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 935a1d9c-20a5-4323-b919-614f45491c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522049953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522049953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522053081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522053081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522056807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522056807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522063610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522063610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522070747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522070747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522074226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522074226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522077465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522077465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522103771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522103771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522107147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522107147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522113008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522113007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522116221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522116221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522121740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522121739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522125046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522125046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522128285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522128285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522131671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522131670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522134627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522134627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522137570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522137569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522140823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522140823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522143752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522143752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522147335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522147335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522150059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522150059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522152844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522152844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522155646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522155646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522158715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522158715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522164479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522164478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522169515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522169515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 6cb008ac-1fc3-4cb2-9285-4f2396828c6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522177558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522177557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_F-G-S"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522181697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522181696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_U-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522186367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522186367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_S-N-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522191579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522191578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_J-S-B"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522195384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522195384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_M-I-S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522200981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522200980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_D-S-R"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522204358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522204358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_D-S-F"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522210822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522210821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_J-B-S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522214044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522214044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_W-T-S"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522217139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522217139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_M-I-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522222899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522222898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3dc5e6d7-30fe-46a8-b235-dc723c85f56f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_S_M-I-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522341583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522341583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2e6a27dd-23a0-4fd0-bb9e-c479052c2a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522844888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522844887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2e6a27dd-23a0-4fd0-bb9e-c479052c2a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522845024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522845024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" f3b3a791-d464-459f-818e-c85ebe76ef60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo usishangae unapoliona pua la nguruwe jinsi lilivyo kwa sababu limekuwa hivyo tangu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522854778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522854778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_M-S-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522858023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522858022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_CH-P-S"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522861046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522861046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_J-S-B"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522864284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522864284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_V-E-S"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522867398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522867398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_N-S-Y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522870714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522870714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_S-V-E"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522873626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522873626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-F-S"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522879013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522879012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-F-S"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522882737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522882737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_E-S-Z"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522887105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522887105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_F-G-S"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522893349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522893349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522899098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522899097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522932476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522932476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" c05b1e29-5103-4f25-b585-fcdd9a770723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522953636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522953635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_U_K"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522960304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522960304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_A_S"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522967011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522967010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_B_S_E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522973653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522973653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_H_T"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522980264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522980264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_S_A"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522986905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522986905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_S_I"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522993546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522993546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_D_U"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523000189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523000189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_H_S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523006815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523006815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_V_S"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523013424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523013424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_S_H"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523026569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523026568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_R_S_H"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523177384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523177381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ca598b52-0943-40c8-b3a3-b6d3e78764f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_R_S_H"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523177513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523177512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" ce7c6186-034e-4983-ac5c-c47abac5c76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523196991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523196991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523200118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523200118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523203573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523203573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523207053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523207053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523219912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523219911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523225332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523225332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523229946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523229946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523233184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523233184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523238515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523238515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523244807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523244807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523248015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523248015"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523264432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523264432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523267424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523267424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523270494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523270494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523274456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523274456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523278107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523278106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523281579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523281579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523285247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523285247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523288481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523288480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523293734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523293734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523296581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523296581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523300020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523300020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523303406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523303405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523306742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523306741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523312496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523312493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2debb40b-94e8-4b4d-ba61-f57811ea999d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523334085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523334085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523337247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523337247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523343894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523343894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523347443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523347443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523350947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523350947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523355523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523355523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523359242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523359241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523362593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523362593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523365782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523365782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523368960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523368960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523375138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523375138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523380553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523380553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523383674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523383674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523386731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523386731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523389826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523389826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523392929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523392928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523395935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523395935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523399226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523399226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523402766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523402766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523405851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523405851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523408919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523408919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523412002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523412002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523415550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523415550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523419014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523419013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523424772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523424771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523434227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523434227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523444029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523444029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523451394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523451394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 2197138e-a149-4844-9b67-6b36845c99b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523460543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523460543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523465799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523465799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523474416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523474416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523477648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523477648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523481577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523481577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523485213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523485213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523488309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523488309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523492289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523492288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523500846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523500846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523507562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523507562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523510768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523510768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523516394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523516394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523523391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523523391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523528989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523528989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523535856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523535856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523539562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523539562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523544149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523544149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523550468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523550468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523557353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523557353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523563193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523563193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523567730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523567730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523573247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523573247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523579626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523579626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523582627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523582627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523586838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523586838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523611257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523611257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523614567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523614567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523620314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523620313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" b9aa6638-4914-4c92-bdb9-5e2d9c334253"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523636893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523636893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523640535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523640535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523643990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523643990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523647897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523647897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523651643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523651643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523654944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523654944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523657849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523657848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523660996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523660995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523666626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523666626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523669678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523669678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523672824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523672824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523681908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523681908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523685304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523685304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523688200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523688200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523692014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523692014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523695058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523695058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523697920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523697920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523700740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523700739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523707414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523707414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523711640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523711640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523714658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523714658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523717555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523717555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523720966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523720966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523724081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523724080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523727189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523727189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523732941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523732940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523741747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523741746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523746796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523746795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 72f490a2-6f58-42be-85db-7fe9da3ed812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523755927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523755927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Y-W"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523758799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523758799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-V-A"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523762409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523762409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_CH-L-T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523766781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523766781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-R-W"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523769935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523769935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-G-A"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523774497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523774497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Y-U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523778039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523778038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-V-T"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523782240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523782240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_S-P-T"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523785483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523785483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_O-N-T"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523788972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523788972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-K-T"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523794722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523794721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-K-T"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523802092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523802091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" a0ef21ae-ece5-4d7a-8230-b65d92df325f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-K-T"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523810805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523810805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-U-D"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523817729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523817729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_G-S-T"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523822288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523822288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_B-V-T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523827900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523827900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-F"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523831346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523831346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523840405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523840404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Z-V-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523851733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523851733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Y-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523856558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523856558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_N-T-P"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523860577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523860577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_F-J-T"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523864589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523864588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-E-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523870346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523870346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 517234a1-f1a1-47fb-8b1d-b76d38c4bafc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-E-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523883163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523883163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_G-S-T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523886934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523886934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-U-D"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523893355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523893354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_F-J-T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523899315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523899314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_N-T-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523902651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523902650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Z-V-T"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523905572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523905572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Y-O"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523910107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523910107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-E-B"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523913802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523913802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-F"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523917378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523917378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_B-V-T"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523921470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523921470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523927238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523927238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523934528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523934528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523939465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523939465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 42fc25ae-675d-420e-9124-d82588329dfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523950997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523950997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523953709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523953709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523955314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523955314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523958339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523958338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523959905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523959904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523962804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523962804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523964367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523964366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523967026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523967026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523968579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523968579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523971544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523971544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523973114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523973114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523976127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523976127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523977696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523977696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523980440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523980440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523982008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523982008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523984949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523984949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523986505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523986505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523989836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523989835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523991397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523991397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523994534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523994534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523996097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523996097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523999456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523999456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524001009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524001009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524008022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524008022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524008283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524008283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524013862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524013862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524020363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524020363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524025495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524025494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524030772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524030771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524034595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524034595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524044219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524044218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524050113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524050112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524065564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524065564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524071296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524071296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524078403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524078403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524084935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524084934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524090721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524090720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524103963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524103963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" e16b44ea-8585-4de4-8531-503790a0ed7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524123055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524123055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524134705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524134705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524142784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524142783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524149236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524149236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524151518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524151518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524153751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524153751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524156638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524156637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524158898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524158898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524161089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524161089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524172135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524172135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524177312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524177311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524184197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524184197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524190419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524190418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524192680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524192680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524199419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524199419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524202493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524202493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524204832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524204832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524207160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524207160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524210198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524210198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524212300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524212299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524214422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524214422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524217529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524217529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524219695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524219695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524221918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524221918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524225040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524225040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524227642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524227609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524231493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524231493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524234593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524234593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524236878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524236878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524239161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524239161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524242292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524242292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524247546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524247546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524249770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524249770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524252796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524252796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524255138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524255138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524257453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524257453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524260611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524260611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524263006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524263006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524265383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524265383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524268376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524268376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524273353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524273352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524285060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524285060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524288550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524288550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524290829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524290827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524293136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524293136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524297771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524297771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524300312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524300312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524302800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524302798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524311208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524311207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524313400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524313399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524315548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524315547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524318897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524318897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524321185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524321185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524323511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524323511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524326607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524326607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524328851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524328850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524331091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524331091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524334224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524334223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524336349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524336349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524338471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524338471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524341598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524341598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524343825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524343825"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524346080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524346080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524349251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524349250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524351462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524351462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524353685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524353685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524356945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524356945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524359266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524359266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524361581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524361580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524364781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524364781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524367077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524367077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524369396","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524369396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524372802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524372801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524372933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524372933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524386068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524386068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524397283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524397282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524429584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524429584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 583c163e-2d6d-468d-b46f-5da0aea5e546"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524438523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524438523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-H-S"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524441402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524441402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-V-A"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524444471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524444471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_E-U-P"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524447754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524447754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-E-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524451089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524451089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_K-U-D"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524455421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524455421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_A-U-S"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524458739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524458739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524462804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524462804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_P-M-U"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524468760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524468760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_P-H-U"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524472991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524472990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-L-R"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524478768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524478767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 1afde308-ee11-42d2-a2a5-28fad27b89b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-L-R"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524496149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524496148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-V-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524504463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524504463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-V-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524510027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524510027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_P-H-U"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524515739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524515739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-H-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524531794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524531794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-L-R"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524542112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524542112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524550221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524550220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524554379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524554378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-E-U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524558164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524558164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_P-M-U"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524562646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524562646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_A-U-S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524566467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524566467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_E-U-P"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524569965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524569964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_K-U-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524575726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524575726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_K-U-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524587341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524587341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_K-U-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524609200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524609200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" bed1bace-3e46-4037-a861-0b441cc86e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_K-U-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524616776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524616776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3057095d-3674-4a31-92ab-bae607841cd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-O-M"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524621588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524621588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3057095d-3674-4a31-92ab-bae607841cd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_K-U-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524624592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524624592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3057095d-3674-4a31-92ab-bae607841cd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-J"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524627074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524627073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3057095d-3674-4a31-92ab-bae607841cd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-J"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524632295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524632294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3057095d-3674-4a31-92ab-bae607841cd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-J"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524641165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524641165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3057095d-3674-4a31-92ab-bae607841cd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-J"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524659978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524659977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3057095d-3674-4a31-92ab-bae607841cd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-J"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524677547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524677546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_195544"," gameId":" 3057095d-3674-4a31-92ab-bae607841cd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-J"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}